Here's two plyometrics that you could throw into your regimen to be able to get more lower
body power.
Number one, we go from a seated where we go both feet bilateral, right?
Athletes trying to stay tight in the trunk, trying to keep the trunk upright and generate
all the force through the lower body.
I want you to think more like I'm generating all my force through the ground, so I really
need you to focus on that, almost like you're jumping with the ball in and then last minute
you extend.
Then the second one, we go into a sprinter step up position, we'll have to get a little
bit of momentum and then works off that single leg or unilateral.
There's two plyometrics that you could--